<form>
	<field>
		<id>network.enabled</id>
		<label>Enabled</label>
		<type>checkbox</type>
		<help>Enable this Network</help>
	</field>
	<field>
		<id>network.name</id>
		<label>Name</label>
		<type>text</type>
		<help>Name of the of the network (Max 12 lowercase and dash characters)</help>
	</field>
    <field>
        <id>network.description</id>
        <label>Description</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help>Description of this AoR (Not Parsed)</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>network.ipv4Enabled</id>
        <label>IPv4</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help>Adds private IPv4 to all nodes in a network.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>network.ipv4CIDR</id>
        <label>IPv4 CIDR</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help>IPv4 CIDR Value (e.g.: w.x.y.z/s)</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>network.ipv6Enabled</id>
        <label>IPv6</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help>Adds private IPv6 to all nodes in a network.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>network.ipv6CIDR</id>
        <label>IPv6 CIDR</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help>Adds private IPv6 to all nodes in a network.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>network.udpHolePunch</id>
        <label>UDP Hole Punching</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help>UDP Hole Punching enables the server to perform STUN. This means, when nodes check-in, the server will record return addresses and ports. It will then communicate this information to the other nodes when they check in, allowing them to reach their peers more easily. This setting is usually good to turn on, with some noteable exceptions. This setting can also break peer-to-peer functionality if, for whatever reason, nodes are unable to reach the server. This can enhance connectivity in cases where NAT may block communication.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>network.defaultAccess</id>
        <label>Default Access Control</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help>Indicates the default ACL value for a node when it joins in respect to it’s peers (enabled or disabled).</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>network.isPointToSite</id>
        <label>Point to Site</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help>Create a network in which all clients have only one, central peer.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>network.isLocalNetwork</id>
        <label>Local Network</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help>This is almost always best to leave this turned off and is left for very special circumstances. If you are running a data center or a private WAN, you may want to enable this setting. It defines the range that nodes will set for Endpoints. Usually, Endpoints are just the public IP. But in some cases, you don’t want any nodes to be reachable via a public IP, and instead want to use a private range. Use if the server is on the same network (LAN) as you.</help>
    </field>
</form>